Denise Caruso papers M1727
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Denise Caruso papers
Undated
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Caruso, Denise
M1727
7.25 Linear Feet (11 boxes, 2 cassette boxes)
Scope and Contents
Materials include Caruso's work about technology in Silicon Valley; conference papers; promotional material. Also includes videos and CD's/DVD's.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Denise Caruso in 2009.
Biographical / Historical
Denise Caruso is an American journalist and analyst specializing in the industries of digital technology and biotechnology. She is the Founder and Executive Director of The Hybrid Vigor Institute, a non-profit think tank created in 2000 that emphasizes cross-sector collaboration. She currently lives and works in San Francisco, California.
Caruso, Denise
- Serious Games: Improving Public Policy through Game-based Learning Simulation (Box 1)
- Protecting America's Freedom in teh Information Age (Box 1)
- Silicon Valley Toxics Coalition Newsletter (Box 1)
- The second Conference on Computers, Freedom and Privacy (Box 1)
- Slides (Box 1)
- Sony on Smart Phones (Box 1)
- The Competitive Benefits from 3D Computing (Box 1)
- News Releases (Box 1)
- Serving the Community: A Public Interest Vision of the National Information Infrastructure (Box 1)
- Setting a new Course for Science and Technology Policy (Box 1)
- Global Information infrastructure: Agenda for Cooperation (Box 1)
- Siggraph (Box 1)
- Iowa Law Review vol. 81 no. 1, 1996 (Box 1)
- Public Support for Free Speech in the US (Box 1)
- Center for the Public Domain (Box 2)
- Glare-Tech (Box 2)
- League for Programming Freedom (Box 2)
- Pauline - SRL (Box 2, Box-folder 1)
- VR Clips/Traub (Box 2, Box-folder 2)
- Virtual World (Box 2, Box-folder 3)
- Visicorp (Box 2, Box-folder 4)
- WAIS (Box 2, Box-folder 5)
- EPA Silicon Valley (Box 2)
- The Hybrid Vigor Institute (Box 3)
- Engineering Reserach Centers (Box 3)
- Second Conference on Computers, Freedom, and Privacy CFP-2 (Box 3)
- AIGA 8th Biennial National Design Conference (Box 3)
- Voices on the Commons Reader (Box 3)
- ComerNet (Box 3, Box-folder 1)
- Salzburg 2000/Oct. (Box 4, Box-folder 1)
- Clippings (Box 4, Box-folder 2)
- Asst. Clips (Tech'y) (Box 4, Box-folder 3)
- Caruso Features! (Box 4, Box-folder 4)
- RS Bill pay final pgs (Box 4, Box-folder 5)
- Online groceries/RS (Box 4, Box-folder 6)
- SL96 Postcon (Box 4, Box-folder 9)
- Diller-Speech (Box 4, Box-folder 11)
- SL96 Promo materials (Box 4, Box-folder 12)
- SL96 Demo Potentials (Box 4, Box-folder 13)
- SL96 Agreement etc. (Box 4, Box-folder 14)
- SL97 mktg plan (Box 4, Box-folder 15)
- Intellectual Prop Copyright Society of the USA Multimedia - What Does it Mean to Lawyers 2/94 (Box 4, Box-folder 16)
- RAND (Box 4, Box-folder 17)
- SL96 Precedings (Box 4, Box-folder 8)
- Spotlight 96 Speakers (Box 4, Box-folder 10)
- SL Speakers Program (Box 4, Box-folder 7)
- Milia D'Or Documents (Box 4, Box-folder 18)
- NME94/Blue Sky/eval'n (Box 4, Box-folder 19)
- Markle U-Access Feb 99 (Box 4, Box-folder 20)
- Getty Conf. 1998 (Box 4, Box-folder 21)
- AIGA Sept 30th (Box 4, Box-folder 22)
- Open Society/Media BD. (Box 4, Box-folder 23)
- Everything we know is wrong - Myth and business (Box 4)
- Online Developers Conference (Box 5)
- Online Behavior Change and disease Management (Box 6)
- Nieman Foundation (Box 6, Box-folder 1)
- Nieman May 95 (Box 6, Box-folder 2)
- Nieman (Box 6, Box-folder 3)
- The Globalization of Culture (Box 6)
- The Sile - Red Burns (Box 6, Box-folder 4)
- National Comm. Forum Oct 91 (Box 6, Box-folder 5)
- MILIA January 1995 (Box 6, Box-folder 6)
- Upside - MS (Box 6, Box-folder 7)
- Final People Page (Box 6, Box-folder 8)
- Microsoft factpack 6-96 (Box 6, Box-folder 9)
- Video and Audio Cassettes (Box 7)
- Warner New Media (Box 8, Box-folder 1)
- MSFT/Net Action (Box 8, Box-folder 2)
- UCCZB (Box 8, Box-folder 3)
- Internet (Box 8, Box-folder 4)
- Viacom Catro Valley (Box 8, Box-folder 5)
- Videoconferencing (Box 8, Box-folder 6)
- Videotex/Teleconf. (Box 8, Box-folder 7)
- Virtual reality (Box 8, Box-folder 8)
- Ted3 Stuff (Box 8, Box-folder 9)
- Digital Media, vol 1 - vol 4 (Box 9)
- Technology & Media (Box 9)
- Consumer Web Watch (Box 9)
- Women in Technology (Box 10, Box-folder 1)
- Electronic Frontier Foundation (Box 10)
- Business Cards (Cassette 12)
- Business Cards (Cassette 11)
- Inside Silicon Valley 1990 (Box 13, Box-folder 1)
- Inside Silicon Valley 1991 (Box 13, Box-folder 2)
- Insider Clips (Box 13, Box-folder 3)
- New Yorker galley proof (Box 13, Box-folder 4)